shr77.com 2014-10-09

# CPV.LI - Free URL Shortener, Image Hosting, Video Hosting, Sharing : Privacy.

We encourage you to read this policy to learn more about what information of yours we collect and how we use it. 

The CPV.LI website accessible via http://www.cpv.li is owned by CPV Media LLC, a Nevada limited liability company. As used in this Agreement, " **we** ", " **us** ", and " **our** " refers to CPV Media LLC. This policy provides you with details on the information we collect from you, the uses we make of your personal information and how we protect your information. If you do not want us to access or using your personal information as described herein, please do not provide us with any. This policy may be updated from time to time without prior notice, so please check back periodically. If you continue to visit this website and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes. 

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs);
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);
  * To administer a promotion, survey or other site feature; or
  * To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account, in addition to receiving occasional updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential. 

Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard drive through your Web browser that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Address: CPV.LI, 7345 S Durango Dr #B107-284, Las Vegas, NV 89113  
Phone: +1 (775) 434.8718  
Fax: +1 (775) 245.7110  
Email: contact@cpv.li
